module is an IntelliJ IDEA are a
模块是IntelliJ IDEA是
collection of sources and other related
资料来源及其他相关资料
resources that IntelliJ IDEA will use to
IntelliJ IDEA将用于的资源
build your project with and these are
建立您的项目，这些是
sources that you have control over so as
您可以控制的来源
opposed to dependencies you can actually
相对于依赖，您实际上可以
go in and edit them and add inter
进入并编辑它们并添加内部
dependencies in between your different
您之间的依赖关系
modules in your project and so forth and
项目中的模块等等
you can think of them as their own sort
您可以将它们视为自己的类型
of self-contained project and so you can
独立的项目，因此您可以
go in and edit their language level and
进入并编辑他们的语言水平，
other dependencies and there are three
其他依赖项，有三个
or four main things that I'd like to go
或我想去的四件事
over in this lesson first is adding a
在本课中，首先添加一个
new module from scratch and then will
从头开始创建新模块，然后将
import a new module an existing module
将新模块导入现有模块
and then we'll show how you can group
然后我们将展示如何分组
them together and do other interesting
他们在一起，做其他有趣的事
things in their settings so first in
事情在他们的设置，所以首先
order to create a new module from
为了从中创建一个新模块
scratch will select great new module
从头开始会选择很棒的新模块
here and just like before we'll select a
在这里，就像我们选择一个
module type and any frameworks or other
模块类型和任何框架或其他
resources that we'd like to use with our
我们想与我们一起使用的资源
module so these frameworks or assets as
模块，因此这些框架或资产
they're called our collection of
他们被称为我们的收藏
technologies and other tools you can use
您可以使用的技术和其他工具
when you're building your project so
当您构建项目时，
you'll need to select an SDK for each of
您需要为每个选择一个SDK
these and maybe an application server if
这些，如果可能，还可能是应用程序服务器
you're using the web application
您正在使用网络应用程序
framework then you can click Next and
框架，然后您可以单击下一步，然后
you can create the module by a name and
您可以通过名称创建模块，然后
add a content root will be here in the
添加内容根目录将在此处
main quick starts directory here and
主要快速启动目录在这里和
then we can call this a new sample
那么我们可以称之为新样本
module and that will be created right
模块，它将被正确创建
under this project directory here and
在此项目目录下，
you can see the project is grouped into
您可以看到该项目被分组为
some different modules here and these
这里有一些不同的模块
are module groups you see up top and
是您在顶部看到的模块组，
individual modules you'll see below if
您将在下面看到的各个模块
you go into one of these you can edit
你进入其中之一，你可以编辑
them by opening up module settings by
通过打开模块设置
pressing ctrl s you can see that each of
按Ctrl可以看到每个
these has their own individual settings
这些都有自己的个人设置
that we can configure
我们可以配置
and they have their sources have
他们有他们的来源
independencies you can set a module SDK
您可以设置模块SDK的独立性
and edit the class paths any other
并编辑其他任何类的路径
resources that you'll need to build that
您将需要的资源
particular module and so forth okay and
特定的模块等等，好吧，
each of these modules are stored inside
每个模块都存储在内部
a dependency storage format called an
依赖存储格式，称为
IML file or an idea module file right
IML文件或构思模块文件权限
you can use that or an eclipse file if
您可以使用该文件或Eclipse文件（如果
you're importing one we'll just
您正在导入一个，我们将
demonstrate how to import an external
演示如何导入外部
module right now so if you have a module
模块，所以如果你有一个模块
that you'd like to import into your
您想导入到您的
project you can select file and open up
您可以选择文件并打开的项目
import module and here you will just
导入模块，在这里您将
select another project that you're
选择另一个您要的项目
working with in IntelliJ IDEA and say
在IntelliJ IDEA中使用并说
this project has an IML file in the root
该项目的根目录中有一个IML文件
directory so we'll select that we'll
目录，所以我们选择
click OK and now that new module will be
单击确定，现在新模块将
important to our project and we should
对我们的项目很重要，我们应该
be able to see that momentarily so this
能够马上看到
is a top-level module and if we'd like
是顶级模块，如果我们愿意
to move where that is inside our project
移动到项目内部的位置
you can do that by right clicking and
您可以通过右键单击并
you can move module to particular group
您可以将模块移至特定组
so you can move it inside this JBoss
因此您可以将其移动到此JBoss中
module that's module group so you can
模块即模块组，因此您可以
select here to this group and then that
在这里选择这个组，然后
will be relocated inside this module
将在此模块内重定位
group ok if you'd like to group together
如果您想一起分组，可以分组
one or more modules you can cut by
您可以削减的一个或多个模块
selecting them right-clicking and then
右键单击选择它们，然后
you can select move module to a new out
您可以选择将模块移至新的位置
level group or subgroup you can call
您可以呼叫的级别组或子组
this say CDI this will be added to this
这个说CDI这将被添加到这个
module group here and you can move that
模块组在这里，您可以将其移动
around and you can configure the module
周围，​​您可以配置模块
group settings and these groups will
组设置，这些组将
just help you categorize all of your
只是帮助您将所有分类
different modules if you'd like to
如果您愿意，可以使用不同的模块
remove a module from your project you
从您的项目中删除模块
can select it and then click the remove
可以选择它，然后单击“删除”
module button and it won't be deleted on
模块按钮，它不会在上删除
disk but it'll just be D index from your
磁盘，但它只是您的D索引
project structure now it should be a
项目结构现在应该是
little more familiar with how modules
稍微熟悉模块
work on
从事于
have any more questions or comments
还有其他问题或意见
please feel free to add them in the
请随时将它们添加到
section below and we'll be happy to get
下面的部分，我们将很高兴获得
back to you as soon as we can
我们会尽快回复您
thanks for watching and develop with
感谢您的关注和发展
pleasure
乐趣